time to go to work
oh can we get ice cream before it's ice
cream before they do the thing you're
right let's get milkshakes you know what
no I love frozen milk treats I'm not
gonna apologize seat belt was messed up
I wasn't my fault
[Music]
Chester Hammond right uh yeah can I help
you oh that depends let's just let's
just get into it um so this isn't gonna
be easy cuz you're great and we know
you're great that cherry pie that you
made for the company picnic that wasn't
store-bought you made that with with
love you care about the people here yeah
thanks How Do You Know Who I am you
realize that we're on the brink of
another recession and some tough choices
are gonna have to be made you've been
with the company 50 G's 15 years you
worked here
I'm sorry I think you have the wrong guy
buddy so we're gonna have to let you go
we who's we do you work here you know
though I would I would never work here I
have no idea what you do the it's a
labyrinth all the offices are empty
looks like Vanilla Sky in here did Roger
put you up to I'm supposed to meet with
my boss right now so that's good that's
good yeah no this is the meeting and
it's not a prank it's it's an app that
looks like a picture your parents oh I'm
so sorry one second
it's an app
see we grant wishes for people let me
show you let me show you all right show
me I guess we grant wishes for people
like anything you want music lessons
deliveries like will show up to your
dad's funeral will like visit your
grandma on the nursing home type thing
so your boss calls the nearest genie
which is me to fire you which is you
because they're not good at eye contact
which I mean to be fair
[Music]
what are you doing I contact see you're
uncomfortable yeah I just got fired by a
guy doesn't gonna work here what am I
gonna do you can be a job who are you
sorry I'm Luke I'm a genie - when did
you get here
oh I snuck in during the hike on that
thing that was awesome and you were
locked in my job
you're Chester you're the guy we're
firing awesome look okay point is why
are anybody right now man it's open
season they hired me my name is not even
Luke I just found a resume Kinkos and
ran with it you know thought you gotta
do it your name's not Luke
[Music]
see my contact we learned about it in
training
oh no no hey Chester Chester Chester it
is over it's over just being honest with
them but your new life's just beginning
get in the lamp it's our catchphrase if
you start working with us that's
something that you never have to say
that's a thing that he says he's trying
to make a catch on it we'll never catch
on
I catch on if we get new people to say
it how do you sign up I guess yes let me
show you
it's alarmingly easy all right so you
know I was putting here like socials and
stuff all right no I don't want to work
with him I don't want to work with him
he looks like 12 eggs a day 12 with a
devil no with a gallon of the milk I'm
surprised he's still alive like you
should be dead Josh I think we gotta get
some of these for the car man these are
awesome
Oh Chester before we go do you guys
validate he is not the one to ask why
would you ask him that oh because he got
fired
oh that sucks I can't believe this is
happening I went to college okay hold on
a second
where is your tux I don't care enough
about this job to rent a tux for one
hour I'll have you know I didn't rent
this I found it in the garbage you look
like a 40 8th grader
ha ha hilarious
[Music]
this place is a bummer remind me how
this happened
gloom bailed this morning but family
spent a lot of money obviously really so
she hired a genie to marry
yes to marry I can't waste the whole
wedding cuz teller got feet that I
have ceremony please I'm not supposed to
look at you before the wedding this is
for the rest of your life oh please no
marriage is for the rest of your life
stupid plus but he's kind of cute you
mean it yeah I probably work something
out
I just can't look Jill did they put a
deposit down it's not refundable they'll
freak out but they're not gonna care if
you marry a stranger
no one's met my fiance I don't need
people in my business so go in there and
sell this thing okay Frankenstein yeah
everybody's watching the next man who
rules my big day dies come on ring boy
let's go
[Music]
Wow
it's like really hot right like that
that was crazy and me and total package
if I want to know like I am so excited
for our honeymoon in Barbados I'm gonna
send you tons of pics it's gonna be
crazy
wait they're paying for you going on
honeymoon Josh I'm her husband what's in
there empty head I'm just kidding I'm so
excited that you're here
supporting me and I wouldn't have anyone
else by my side that's my best man I'm
not your best man should be me I'm fun
[Music]
Tucker you look a little different than
I remember
I got I got a little taller at a growth
spurt
who the hell is that I have no idea you
were an african-american gentleman when
I met you
father please ma'am I hope you can pay
twice for this are you with me what
trouble okay
you don't think I've played this game
before kill you
[Music]
anyone has any objections to the union
between Tina and Tucker speak now or
forever
oh never had an objection before look
you don't have to marry him okay
sleeps in a racecar bed he can't even
read I can learn I can hey hey you leave
Tucker alone you will not get in the way
of my love you don't even know him
firstly okay I now pronounce you husband
and wife
you may kiss your bride
[Music]
[Applause]
so I'm at Home Depot right and the guys
like buddy you're looking for Office
Depot okay and then I woke up not going
back to jail sorry sir
[Music]
oh wow that was terrible for me neither
one of us can judge the other person for
how they reacted back there did you yes
Oh grow up okay what me grow up he said
we were not gonna judge you said that I
didn't say that okay that's fair
but let's just move on okay well we got
one who is it well it's a quarter-mile
behind us on the street you don't think
yeah I think yeah let's just pull the
whole thing around just pull a u-turn or
something yeah nope no need mirrors
hey Ari
you gotta understand I think my biggest
phobia is somebody jumping on my
windshield nothing you do with the blood
or anything and you could have been a
homeless man jumping up trying to bite
us or something like we don't we don't
know you I mean we don't at all anyway
it says you want to go to 145 Maple
Street yes the hospital man I broke my
leg oh it looks like Alfred Hitchcock
his profile sir we're gonna get you to
the hospital right on time
that's the genii guarantee thank you
yeah what if I rub on the car and wish
for a back seat yeah how are we gonna
thick Captain Ahab back here huh you
barely fit the top sound actually
travels if you didn't know at 141 miles
per second okay that's good this is step
one and it's slowly pushing towards you
okay we're gonna get you to the hospital
sir I need you stop what's the bacon one
if you are on this side then we can't
drive the neck I have to break his other
leg Josh that's a priest oh well we
could make it look like an accident
what nothing sir everything's fine keep
calm we are not doing that okay we're
gonna have to do it my way no yes no no
thank you come on dude take one for the
team
no no thank you no yes I happen so I'm
at Home Depot and the guys like buddy
you're looking for Office Depot and then
I woke up
dude that that's my dream oh yeah it is
now sir this is a nightmare
you